thetripclip.com 2015-07-18

# The Trip Clip - Privacy Policy

We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. **By visiting TheTripClip.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

What Personal Information About Customers Does TheTripClip.com Gather?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at TheTripClip.com. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way.  This information includes your name, address, email, and any personal information you choose to give us to help us get to know our customers better (your age, gender, number of kids, etc). 
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, when you create a list, or choose a word search to print out, we store the content of your printable pages in our database.
  * **Credit Card Information:**   We do NOT store any credit card information at TheTripClip.com.  We use PayPal to handle all of our credit card transactions.  PayPal is PCI Compliant. [ Click here](http://usa.visa.com/download/merchants/cisp-list-of-pcidss-compliant-service-providers.pdf) to verify PayPal's PCI Compliance. [ Click here](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside) to learn more about how PayPal keeps your information safe.

What About Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize you and help you access any Activities you've purchased at TheTripClip.com.

Does TheTripClip.com Share the Information It Receives?

No. Personally identifiable information such as name, mailing address, phone number, e-mail address, is not passed along to any other company and such information is collected only when needed to fulfill a customer's request.

How Secure Is Information About Me?

We do not store any credit card information on our site.

Which Information Can I Access?

TheTripClip.com offers a complete list of all of the Activities you've purchased, and you can use the My Account page to view those activities and print them again at any time.  You can also use this page to access and in some cases edit your personal information.

Are Children Allowed to Use TheTripClip.com?

TheTripClip.com does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use TheTripClip.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

What about Spam?

TheTripClip.com will not send unsolicited advertisements (spam).
